{
  "quiz" : [
    {
      "quizOptions" : [
        {
          "question": "Her thinking leans ____ democracy.",
          "answer" : "Towards",
          "options": [
            "With",
            "Towards",
            "For",
            "Of"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "He got too tired _____ over work.",
          "answer" : "Because of",
          "options": [
            "Because of",
            "Because off",
            "On",
            "For"
          ]
        },
        {
            "question": "_____ his principles, he has to be very careful",
            "answer" : "With regard to",
            "options": [
              "With regard on",
              "With regard of",
              "With regard to",
              "With regard for"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "Building has been built _____ the new plan.",
            "answer" : "In accordance with",
            "options": [
              "Accordance to",
              "For",
              "About",
              "In accordance with"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "He crossed the broken bridge ____ warning.",
            "answer" : "In spite of",
            "options": [
              "On",
              "In spite off",
              "In spite of",
              "About"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "The train ____ as fast as the bus.",
            "answer" : "Moves",
            "options": [
              "Went",
              "Going",
              "Moves",
              "Running"
            ]
          }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quizOptions" : [
        {
          "question": "Her thinking leans ____ democracy.",
          "answer" : "Towards",
          "options": [
            "With",
            "Towards",
            "For",
            "Of"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "He got too tired _____ over work.",
          "answer" : "Because of",
          "options": [
            "Because of",
            "Because off",
            "On",
            "For"
          ]
        },
        {
            "question": "_____ his principles, he has to be very careful",
            "answer" : "With regard to",
            "options": [
              "With regard on",
              "With regard of",
              "With regard to",
              "With regard for"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "Building has been built _____ the new plan.",
            "answer" : "In accordance with",
            "options": [
              "Accordance to",
              "For",
              "About",
              "In accordance with"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "He crossed the broken bridge ____ warning.",
            "answer" : "In spite of",
            "options": [
              "On",
              "In spite off",
              "In spite of",
              "About"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "The train ____ as fast as the bus.",
            "answer" : "Moves",
            "options": [
              "Went",
              "Going",
              "Moves",
              "Running"
            ]
          }
      ]
    },
    {
      "quizOptions" : [
        {
          "question": "Her thinking leans ____ democracy.",
          "answer" : "Towards",
          "options": [
            "With",
            "Towards",
            "For",
            "Of"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "He got too tired _____ over work.",
          "answer" : "Because of",
          "options": [
            "Because of",
            "Because off",
            "On",
            "For"
          ]
        },
        {
            "question": "_____ his principles, he has to be very careful",
            "answer" : "With regard to",
            "options": [
              "With regard on",
              "With regard of",
              "With regard to",
              "With regard for"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "Building has been built _____ the new plan.",
            "answer" : "In accordance with",
            "options": [
              "Accordance to",
              "For",
              "About",
              "In accordance with"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "He crossed the broken bridge ____ warning.",
            "answer" : "In spite of",
            "options": [
              "On",
              "In spite off",
              "In spite of",
              "About"
            ]
          },
          {
            "question": "The train ____ as fast as the bus.",
            "answer" : "Moves",
            "options": [
              "Went",
              "Going",
              "Moves",
              "Running"
            ]
          }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
